<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
  <title>StudyGuideindia Management  Colleges</title>
   <category>List of Management colleges in india</category>
   <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/</link>
  <description>List of Management colleges in india</description>
  <image>
      <url>http://studyguideindia.com/res/images/study_guide-logo.jpg</url>
      <title>Studyguideindia.com</title>
      <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/</link>
      <width>244</width>
      <height>70</height>
    </image>
	<item>
      <title>List of Management colleges in India</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/</link>
      <description>List of Management Studies in India  Online information about List of Management Studies in India, address, contact details, List of Management Studies in India course, results, phone number, List of Management Studies in India campus, certificate, Academy of Management Studies syllabus and more.</description>
    </item>
 <item>
      <title>List of Management colleges in Andaman and Nicobar Islands</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=AN</link>
      <description>List of Management Colleges in Andaman and Nicobar Islands, Andaman and Nicobar Islands, best Management Colleges of Andaman and Nicobar Islands, top Management Colleges Andaman and Nicobar Islands india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Andaman and Nicobar Islands India, details, addresses of Andaman and Nicobar Islands Management Colleges, telephones of Andaman and Nicobar Islands Management Colleges.</description>
    </item>
  <item>
	<title>List of Management colleges in Andhra Pradesh</title>
	<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=AP</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Andhra Pradesh, Andhra Pradesh, best Management Colleges of Andhra Pradesh, top Management Colleges Andhra Pradesh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Andhra Pradesh India, details, addresses of Andhra Pradesh Management Colleges, telephones of Andhra Pradesh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Arunachal Pradesh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=AR</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Arunachal Pradesh, Arunachal Pradesh, best Management Colleges of Arunachal Pradesh, top Management Colleges Arunachal Pradesh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Arunachal Pradesh India, details, addresses of Arunachal Pradesh Management Colleges, telephones of Arunachal Pradesh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Assam</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=AS</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Assam, Assam, best Management Colleges of Assam, top Management Colleges Assam india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Assam India, details, addresses of Assam Management Colleges, telephones of Assam Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Bihar</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=BR</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Bihar, Bihar, best Management Colleges of Bihar, top Management Colleges Bihar india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Bihar India, details, addresses of Bihar Management Colleges, telephones of Bihar Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Chandigarh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=CH</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Chandigarh, Chandigarh, best Management Colleges of Chandigarh, top Management Colleges Chandigarh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Chandigarh India, details, addresses of Chandigarh Management Colleges, telephones of Chandigarh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Chhattisgarh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=CT</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Chhattisgarh, Chhattisgarh, best Management Colleges of Chhattisgarh, top Management Colleges Chhattisgarh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Chhattisgarh India, details, addresses of Chhattisgarh Management Colleges, telephones of Chhattisgarh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Daman and Diu</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=DD</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Daman and Diu, Daman and Diu, best Management Colleges of Daman and Diu, top Management Colleges Daman and Diu india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Daman and Diu India, details, addresses of Daman and Diu Management Colleges, telephones of Daman and Diu Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Delhi</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=DL</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Delhi, Delhi, best Management Colleges of Delhi, top Management Colleges Delhi india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Delhi India, details, addresses of Delhi Management Colleges, telephones of Delhi Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Dadra and Nagar Haveli</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=DN</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Dadra and Nagar Haveli, Dadra and Nagar Haveli, best Management Colleges of Dadra and Nagar Haveli, top Management Colleges Dadra and Nagar Haveli india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Dadra and Nagar Haveli India, details, addresses of Dadra and Nagar Haveli Management Colleges, telephones of Dadra and Nagar Haveli Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Goa</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=GA</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Goa, Goa, best Management Colleges of Goa, top Management Colleges Goa india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Goa India, details, addresses of Goa Management Colleges, telephones of Goa Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Gujarat</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=GJ</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Gujarat, Gujarat, best Management Colleges of Gujarat, top Management Colleges Gujarat india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Gujarat India, details, addresses of Gujarat Management Colleges, telephones of Gujarat Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Himachal Pradesh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=HP</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Himachal Pradesh, Himachal Pradesh, best Management Colleges of Himachal Pradesh, top Management Colleges Himachal Pradesh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Himachal Pradesh India, details, addresses of Himachal Pradesh Management Colleges, telephones of Himachal Pradesh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Haryana</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=HR</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Haryana, Haryana, best Management Colleges of Haryana, top Management Colleges Haryana india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Haryana India, details, addresses of Haryana Management Colleges, telephones of Haryana Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Jharkhand</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=JH</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Jharkhand, Jharkhand, best Management Colleges of Jharkhand, top Management Colleges Jharkhand india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Jharkhand India, details, addresses of Jharkhand Management Colleges, telephones of Jharkhand Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in ammu And Kashmir</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=JK</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Jammu And Kashmir, Jammu And Kashmir, best Management Colleges of Jammu And Kashmir, top Management Colleges Jammu And Kashmir india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Jammu And Kashmir India, details, addresses of Jammu And Kashmir Management Colleges, telephones of Jammu And Kashmir Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Karnataka</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=KA</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Karnataka, Karnataka, best Management Colleges of Karnataka, top Management Colleges Karnataka india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Karnataka India, details, addresses of Karnataka Management Colleges, telephones of Karnataka Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Kerala</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=KL</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Kerala, Kerala, best Management Colleges of Kerala, top Management Colleges Kerala india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Kerala India, details, addresses of Kerala Management Colleges, telephones of Kerala Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Lakshadweep</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=LD</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Lakshadweep, Lakshadweep, best Management Colleges of Lakshadweep, top Management Colleges Lakshadweep india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Lakshadweep India, details, addresses of Lakshadweep Management Colleges, telephones of Lakshadweep Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Manipur</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=MN</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Manipur, Manipur, best Management Colleges of Manipur, top Management Colleges Manipur india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Manipur India, details, addresses of Manipur Management Colleges, telephones of Manipur Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Madhya Pradesh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=MP</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Madhya Pradesh, Madhya Pradesh, best Management Colleges of Madhya Pradesh, top Management Colleges Madhya Pradesh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Madhya Pradesh India, details, addresses of Madhya Pradesh Management Colleges, telephones of Madhya Pradesh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Mizoram</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=MZ</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Mizoram, Mizoram, best Management Colleges of Mizoram, top Management Colleges Mizoram india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Mizoram India, details, addresses of Mizoram Management Colleges, telephones of Mizoram Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Nagaland</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=NL</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Nagaland, Nagaland, best Management Colleges of Nagaland, top Management Colleges Nagaland india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Nagaland India, details, addresses of Nagaland Management Colleges, telephones of Nagaland Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Orissa</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=OR</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Orissa, Orissa, best Management Colleges of Orissa, top Management Colleges Orissa india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Orissa India, details, addresses of Orissa Management Colleges, telephones of Orissa Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Punjab</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=PB</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Punjab, Punjab, best Management Colleges of Punjab, top Management Colleges Punjab india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Punjab India, details, addresses of Punjab Management Colleges, telephones of Punjab Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Pondicherry</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=PY</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Pondicherry, Pondicherry, best Management Colleges of Pondicherry, top Management Colleges Pondicherry india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Pondicherry India, details, addresses of Pondicherry Management Colleges, telephones of Pondicherry Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Rajasthan</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=RJ</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Rajasthan, Rajasthan, best Management Colleges of Rajasthan, top Management Colleges Rajasthan india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Rajasthan India, details, addresses of Rajasthan Management Colleges, telephones of Rajasthan Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Sikkim</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=SK</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Sikkim, Sikkim, best Management Colleges of Sikkim, top Management Colleges Sikkim india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Sikkim India, details, addresses of Sikkim Management Colleges, telephones of Sikkim Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Tamil Nadu</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=TN</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Tamil Nadu, Tamil Nadu, best Management Colleges of Tamil Nadu, top Management Colleges Tamil Nadu india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Tamil Nadu India, details, addresses of Tamil Nadu Management Colleges, telephones of Tamil Nadu Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Tripura</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=TR</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Tripura, Tripura, best Management Colleges of Tripura, top Management Colleges Tripura india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Tripura India, details, addresses of Tripura Management Colleges, telephones of Tripura Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Uttaranchal</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=UL</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Uttaranchal, Uttaranchal, best Management Colleges of Uttaranchal, top Management Colleges Uttaranchal india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Uttaranchal India, details, addresses of Uttaranchal Management Colleges, telephones of Uttaranchal Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in Uttar Pradesh</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=UP</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in Uttar Pradesh, Uttar Pradesh, best Management Colleges of Uttar Pradesh, top Management Colleges Uttar Pradesh india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in Uttar Pradesh India, details, addresses of Uttar Pradesh Management Colleges, telephones of Uttar Pradesh Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>List of Management Colleges in West Bengal</title>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:57:34     GMT</pubDate>
    <link>http://www.studyguideindia.com/Colleges/Management-Studies/default.asp?State=WB</link>
    <description>List of Management Colleges in West Bengal, West Bengal, best Management Colleges of West Bengal, top Management Colleges West Bengal india, Indian Management Colleges, Management Colleges in India, Management Colleges in West Bengal India, details, addresses of West Bengal Management Colleges, telephones of West Bengal Management Colleges.</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>